571-232-9287 (cell)

mceraolo@gmail.com

SUMMARY AND SKILLS

Mark possesses a 13-year technical background specializing in Service Desk functions with responsibilities ranging from developing custom SQL scripts, programming a COTS application, creating, maintaining, and reviewing Change and Configuration Management documentation. Mark has experience in the following domains:

- SQL
- webMethods/SoftwareAG
- PowerBuilder
- Sybase ASE
- SPS PD²
- Python

- .Net (VB and C#)
- MS Office suite
- HTML/CSS/Javascript/Bootstrap
- Oracle CRM
- ServiceNow
- XML

CERTIFICATIONS: COMPTIA SECURITY+ CE

EXPERIENCE

MAY 2017 – PRESENT SYSTEM ANALYST 3, CACI, INC.

Responsibilities are to provide functional and technical support for active DoD sites for all branches of the DoD (Army, Air Force, Navy/Marines); provide customer with interim resolutions for software defects and data related errors; provide support for Sybase ASE, Procurement Desktop-Defense (PD²), the PD² Adapter and Federal Procurement Data Systems and standards (FPDS, PDS, GFEBS) software; acting as the main point of contact and Subject Matter Expert (SME) on the Standard Procurement System Help Desk for all technical and functional issues dealing with third-party integration platform (SoftwareAG) and PD² Adapter/ SPS Legacy Integrations related issues.

Takes responsibility for customer issues by actively taking on new issues and following up with existing issues. Performs the following for each issue: 1) Provides accurate resolutions to customer issues. 2) Assesses the severity of the issue to ensure the customer's expectations for the issue are met. 3) Responds to issues in a timely manner and provide customers with an ongoing status of progress for their issues all using Oracle CRM ticket management system.

Supports additional projects as requested by management such as reviewing product documentation (ISO certification documents) and supporting product development testing efforts. Contributes to the overall Customer Support Knowledge Base by creating Frequently Asked Questions, training and mentoring new team members, or working with other team members to provide assistance as needed.

MAY 2016 - APRIL 2017 SYSTEM ANALYST 3, CACI, INC.

i

Responsibilities are to provide functional and technical support to an SAP/ERP environment for the USDA; provide customer with interim resolutions for software defects and data related errors; provide support for WBSCM; acting as the main point of contact and Subject Matter Expert (SME) on the WBSCM Service Desk for technical and functional related issues.

Provides support to end users on a variety of issues. Identifies, researches, and resolves technical problems. Responds to telephone calls, email and personnel requests for technical support. Documents, tracks, and monitors the problem to ensure a timely resolution. Provides second-tier support to end users for either PC, server, or mainframe applications or hardware. Interacts with network services, software systems engineering, and/or applications development to restore service and/or identify and correct core problem.

AUGUST 2007 - MAY 2016 SYSTEM ANALYST 3, CACI, INC.

Responsibilities are to provide functional and technical support for active DoD sites for all branches of the DoD (Army, Air Force, Navy/Marines); provide customer with interim resolutions for software defects and data related errors; provide support for Sybase ASE, Procurement Desktop-Defense (PD²), the PD² Adapter and Federal Procurement Data Systems and standards (FPDS, PDS, GFEBS); acting as the main point of contact and Subject Matter Expert (SME) on the Standard Procurement System Help Desk for all technical and functional issues dealing with third-party integration platform (SoftwareAG) and PD² Adapter/ SPS Legacy Integrations related issues.

Takes responsibility for customer issues by actively taking on new issues and following up with existing issues. Performs the following for each issue: 1) Provides accurate resolutions to customer issues. 2) Assesses the severity of the issue to ensure the customer's expectations for the issue are met. 3) Responds to issues in a timely manner and provide customers with an ongoing status of progress for their issues all using Oracle CRM ticket management system.

Supports additional projects as requested by management such as reviewing product documentation (ISO certification documents) and supporting product development testing efforts. Contributes to the overall Customer Support Knowledge Base by creating Frequently Asked Questions, training and mentoring new team members, or working with other team members to provide assistance as needed. Was the Project/Lead Developer for the SPS Help Desks' COTS application using Powerbuilder 12.5 and 12.6. Lead development, test and roll-out of new version yearly.

NOVEMBER 2006 - JULY 2007 CUSTOMER SUPPORT SPECIALIST, LUCAS SYSTEMS INC.

Troubleshot, researched, diagnosed, documented, and resolved technical issues surrounding the Lucas Voice-Automates software products using Visual Basic. Worked with product development and project teams to track and resolve problems. Participated in and sometimes led the installation of systems at customer sites as well customer training.

OCTOBER 2005 - NOVEMBER 2006 HELP DESK SPECIALIST 2 - TECH SUPPORT, CACI, INC.

Technical troubleshooting and mitigation of software-related issues with the SPS software suite. Formulated resolutions by researching previous similar issues and reference guides. Developed diagnostic and manipulative scripts using SQL to resolve customer issues.

EDUCATION

MAY 2003

B.S. COMPUTER SCIENCE, YOUNGSTOWN STATE UNIVERSITY